翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Now let's go a little further than the mystery of the walrus and talk about what happens when we pass parameters to functions.
学习完海象之谜，讨论一下函数的参数传递
So it turns out that the golden rule of equals also applies to passing of parameters in Java.
事实证明，等号的黄金法则也适用于 Java 中的参数传递
The golden rule of equals, remember,
记住等号的黄金法则
is just given variables b and a,
已知变量 b 和 a
if we say b equals a, we copy all the bits from a into b.
b = a 就是把 a 的所有位复制到 b
So the same thing happens when you pass parameters to a function.
将参数传递给函数时也会发生同样的事情
What you're going to do is whatever bits you want to give to the function are going to be copied to the new scope.
你要给函数提供的任何位都将被复制到新的作用域中
So let's see an example that makes it clear what's going on.
看一个例子来清楚地说明
Here's a function called average.
这是一个叫 average 的函数
It's not very glamorous.
它不深奥
All it does is take a couple of doubles and return their average.
就是返回 double 类型参数的平均值
But we're going to use this as an example of this rule.
我们以此为例来说明这条规则
So when I run main, what it's going to do is first create a double variable that's 64 bits and fill in this box here with 5.5.
运行 main 时，首先创建一个64位的 double 变量，然后用5.5填充这个盒子
Then y will be 10.5.
那么 y 就是10.5
And then finally, we're going to make a call to the average function.
最后要调用 average 函数
So what that means is we're going to take these bits and hand them over, hand copies of them over to the average function,
这意味着我们要把这些位的副本交给 average 函数
and it's going to store them in its own scope.
函数会将它们存储在自己的作用域中
So it's going to have local a and b--
所以会有局部的 a 和 b
these are these variables that are usable only by average--
这些变量只能被 average 使用
and it's going to copy those bits in.
它会把这些位复制进来
So that's the scoop.
这就是作用域
It's not that there's some arrows pointing back.
没有箭头只想后面
Instead, what is happening is the actual bits are copied into these boxes.
而是实际的位被复制到这些盒子中
So notice there's no arrows pointing back.
请注意，没有箭头指向后面
This idea of making actual copies of the bits is sometimes called pass by value.
这种产生位的真实副本的方式有时称为“值传递”
Now we're not really going to use that term so much in our class, but it might be useful to you at some job interview.
课上不会经常使用这个词，但在面试中很有用
But basically, in Java, you always pass by value.
Java 中总是按值传递
In other words, you always copy the bits.
也就是说总是复制这些位
So let's see a little summary of what we've learned so far.
现在看一下我们到目前为止所学内容的小结
And then I'm going to give you guys a challenge to make sure this all makes sense.
然后我会给你们一个挑战确保理解
So to summarize everything we've got so far,
总结一下我们目前掌握的一切
there are nine types of variables in Java.
Java 中有9种类型的变量
First, there are eight primitive types,
有8种基本类型
and then we have a ninth type, or just a set of types,
还有第9种类型，或者称为一组类型
I guess you can say, which is references to objects, which could be planets, arrays, walruses, whatever.
可以说是对对象的引用，可以是行星、数组、海象等等
And those references, we're going to think of them as arrows, but they may also be null.
那些引用被视为箭头，它们也可能是 null
So in this box and pointer notation
在这个盒子和指针表示法中
we're going to use for the rest of the class
我们在课程剩余部分都将使用
and especially with understanding our data structures,
尤其是学习数据结构时
each variable right here is going to be drawn as a box.
每个变量都将被画成一个盒子
And it's going to have a label.
它会有一个标签
So here's a box labeled a, a box labeled b, a box labeled x, and so forth.
这里是标记为 a 的盒子，标记为 b 的盒子，标记为 x 的盒子，以此类推
So every variable is going to have a little box.
每个变量都会有一个小盒子
And we're going to show the values for that variable are going to be shown in that box.
我们会在盒子中显示该变量的值
Now, rather than show a bunch of binary digits,
与其显示一堆二进制数字
we're going to write them in human readable format.
不如以人类可读的格式写出它们
For primitive types, that means writing things like five or 3.5 or a.
对于基本类型，写成类似于5或3.5或 a 的东西
And for reference types, instead of writing out a binary address,
对于引用类型，不会写出二进制地址
we're going to represent it by arrows, which are going to point at specific instances.
而是用箭头表示它，箭头指向具体的实例
And the golden rule in terms of understanding how the equals operator works in Java
理解等号的黄金法则，它在 Java 中是一条金科玉律
and how function parameters are passed is simple.
函数参数的传递方式也很简单
When you say b equals a, you're going to copy the bits.
b = a 就是复制这些位
Whenever you pass parameters, you're going to copy the bits.
无论何时传递参数都要复制这些位
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
That's it.
就这样